[
  {
    "id": "0b524876-0ebc-4526-87e3-262d20b751d7",
    "reference": "1- John 15:2 \u201cEvery branch \u2026 that does not bear fruit\u201d",
    "question": "But that the world may know that I ________ the Father; and as the Father....",
    "options": [
      "Am",
      "See",
      "Respect",
      "Love"
    ],
    "answer": "Love",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0db0b846-a0cf-4946-aa2f-51915e39b85f",
    "reference": "1- John 15:2 \u201cEvery branch \u2026 that does not bear fruit\u201d",
    "question": "Can a branch bear fruit of itself, except it abides in the vine?",
    "options": [
      "Sometimes",
      "No",
      "In some countries",
      "a & c"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c4bd33d4-5dd2-408c-aadb-35ba540dcc13",
    "reference": "2- John 3:16 \u201cGod so loved the world [You!] that He gave His only begotten Son\u201d",
    "question": "According to John 5 who are the branches?",
    "options": [
      "God and Jesus",
      "Jesus",
      "Cannot say",
      "Christians"
    ],
    "answer": "Christians",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c52dbd58-e10a-45b6-ae80-25969c35da71",
    "reference": "2- John 3:16 \u201cGod so loved the world [You!] that He gave His only begotten Son\u201d",
    "question": "Who wrote John 3?",
    "options": [
      "God",
      "Jesus",
      "John",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "John",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c96957e4-04a5-473c-9f4b-39913a3ce9ef",
    "reference": "2- John 3:16 \u201cGod so loved the world [You!] that He gave His only begotten Son\u201d",
    "question": "Except a man be ____ he cannot see the kingdom of God",
    "options": [
      "Singing",
      "Baptized",
      "Kind",
      "Be born again"
    ],
    "answer": "Be born again",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2bfc2e80-c5c8-4264-b564-1eea86e55311",
    "reference": "2- John 3:16 \u201cGod so loved the world [You!] that He gave His only begotten Son\u201d",
    "question": "For every one that doeth evil ___ the light, neither cometh to the ligth......",
    "options": [
      "Adore",
      "Pursue",
      "Hateth",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Hateth",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "372f04fa-b5c6-4ed7-933e-71d3154e4636",
    "reference": "3- Matthew 6:9-15 The Lord\u2019s Prayer",
    "question": "What happens to anyone who believeth in the Son of God (Jesus Christ)?",
    "options": [
      "He is blessed",
      "He serves God",
      "Nothing",
      "He should not perish"
    ],
    "answer": "He should not perish",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0f8114b3-49db-4d11-91a0-6f85c4d85da8",
    "reference": "3- Matthew 6:9-15 The Lord\u2019s Prayer",
    "question": "But when ye pray, use not vain ___?",
    "options": [
      "Words",
      "Repetitions",
      "Signs",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Repetitions",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5eff6aca-6064-4d0f-9132-09273db9439b",
    "reference": "3- Matthew 6:9-15 The Lord\u2019s Prayer",
    "question": "But if ye forgive not men their trespasses, ___ will your Father forgive your trespasses.",
    "options": [
      "So",
      "Neither",
      "But",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Neither",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0a2e964a-5968-47b1-a550-c5166b98e956",
    "reference": "3- Matthew 6:9-15 The Lord\u2019s Prayer",
    "question": "But I say unto you, ___ your enemies, bless them that curse you, do good to them that hate you...",
    "options": [
      "Avoid",
      "Bless",
      "Punish",
      "Love"
    ],
    "answer": "Love",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1b6424ac-e9d9-4e49-a4ff-10670c921899",
    "reference": "3- Matthew 6:9-15 The Lord\u2019s Prayer",
    "question": "Who is the author of Psalm 23?",
    "options": [
      "James",
      "Mark",
      "Matthew",
      "King David"
    ],
    "answer": "King David",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "10f73672-7491-459f-a376-a8a6d42e6b82",
    "reference": "3- Matthew 6:9-15 The Lord\u2019s Prayer",
    "question": "Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will ___ no evil....",
    "options": [
      "See",
      "Contemplate",
      "Fear",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Fear",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a39b0965-066f-4b8b-bfdd-f6d660ec597b",
    "reference": "5- Psalm 1:3 \u201c[You] shall be like a tree planted by the rivers of water\u201d",
    "question": "Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me ___ the days of my life....",
    "options": [
      "Some of",
      "In the darkest of",
      "All",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f77af693-5d30-46c1-acec-15775d70ec6b",
    "reference": "5- Psalm 1:3 \u201c[You] shall be like a tree planted by the rivers of water\u201d",
    "question": "But his delight is in the ___ of the Lord; and his law doth the meditate day and night",
    "options": [
      "Power",
      "Strength",
      "Mercies",
      "Law"
    ],
    "answer": "Law",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "55fea14d-4d01-48b2-8798-f06166d5c5d6",
    "reference": "5- Psalm 1:3 \u201c[You] shall be like a tree planted by the rivers of water\u201d",
    "question": "For the Lord ____ the way of righteous: but the way of the ungodly shall perish.",
    "options": [
      "Knoweth",
      "Acknowledge",
      "Strengthen",
      "Bless"
    ],
    "answer": "Knoweth",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1bac2e22-d5bd-4db4-a46f-48fd665db034",
    "reference": "6- Psalm 138:8 \u201cThe Lord will perfect that which concerns me\u201d",
    "question": "Serve the Lord with ____, and rejoice with trembling.",
    "options": [
      "Your mind",
      "Fear",
      "Your body",
      "a & c"
    ],
    "answer": "Fear",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5aabcf7b-d0ff-4098-9fc4-d7e3337bd35a",
    "reference": "6- Psalm 138:8 \u201cThe Lord will perfect that which concerns me\u201d",
    "question": "I will praise thee with my whole ____: before the gods will I sing praise unto thee.",
    "options": [
      "Being",
      "Mind",
      "Heart",
      "Household"
    ],
    "answer": "Heart",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1c539cc6-51ef-4639-b7ec-91a20f297a0b",
    "reference": "7- Romans 10:17 \u201cFaith comes by hearing\u201d",
    "question": "Though the Lord be high, yet hath he respect unto the ___: but the proud he knoweth afar off.",
    "options": [
      "Faithful",
      "Wise",
      "Lowly",
      "Kind"
    ],
    "answer": "Lowly",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "24e8c595-1d18-4c52-bfa6-935468ed9bcc",
    "reference": "7- Romans 10:17 \u201cFaith comes by hearing\u201d",
    "question": "For the scriptures saith, whosoever believeth on him shall not be ____.",
    "options": [
      "Destroyed",
      "Ashamed",
      "Mocked",
      "Killed"
    ],
    "answer": "Ashamed",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "42d69f77-7c1d-47e7-95b7-afab38e893da",
    "reference": "7- Romans 10:17 \u201cFaith comes by hearing\u201d",
    "question": "And how shall they preach, except they be ___?",
    "options": [
      "Taught",
      "Christian",
      "Sent",
      "Ready"
    ],
    "answer": "Sent",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "63bd60f8-68cd-4818-879d-1c29a7c55263",
    "reference": "8- Psalm 32:7 \u201cYou are my hiding place\u201d",
    "question": "How does faith come?",
    "options": [
      "Through trusting God",
      "By hearing and hearing by the word of God",
      "By attending church regularly",
      "Through the help of the holy spirit"
    ],
    "answer": "By hearing and hearing by the word of God",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e07b19e6-4281-47fb-9a36-142fd2d7bcab",
    "reference": "8- Psalm 32:7 \u201cYou are my hiding place\u201d",
    "question": "I will confess my transgressions unto the Lord; and thou ____ the iniquity of my sin.",
    "options": [
      "Listened to",
      "Washed",
      "Forgavest",
      "Chastise"
    ],
    "answer": "Forgavest",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "43e5db43-d44c-4822-bde3-c1a961dc9ed4",
    "reference": "8- Psalm 32:7 \u201cYou are my hiding place\u201d",
    "question": "Be of good courage, and he shall ____ your heart, all ye that hope in the Lord.",
    "options": [
      "Bless",
      "Support",
      "Strengthen",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Strengthen",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3e047f63-9ff5-4f65-b9df-56befd4d77a9",
    "reference": "8- Psalm 32:7 \u201cYou are my hiding place\u201d",
    "question": "I will ___ thee and teach thee in the way which thou shalt go: I will guide thee with mine eye.",
    "options": [
      "Cast",
      "Anoint",
      "Bless",
      "Instruct"
    ],
    "answer": "Instruct",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "925c1a3c-2c1c-4107-938c-d4a0e12e3806",
    "reference": "8- Psalm 32:7 \u201cYou are my hiding place\u201d",
    "question": "Be glad in the Lord, and ___ ye righteous: and shout for joy, all ye that are upright in heart",
    "options": [
      "Praise",
      "Worship",
      "Honor",
      "a & c"
    ],
    "answer": "",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cba577cc-eaf6-45c2-b004-11f73274d207",
    "reference": "8- Psalm 32:7 \u201cYou are my hiding place\u201d",
    "question": "The righteous cry, and the Lord heareth, and ___ them out of all their troubles.",
    "options": [
      "Restore",
      "Delivereth",
      "Support",
      "Bring"
    ],
    "answer": "Delivereth",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a7061bd2-1962-44ca-b00d-b2ddc7c4f91e",
    "reference": "8- Psalm 32:7 \u201cYou are my hiding place\u201d",
    "question": "Come, ye children, hearken unto me: I will teach you the ___ of the Lord",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Way",
      "Kindness",
      "Fear"
    ],
    "answer": "Fear",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f815b04a-619e-4aa7-b39b-0a97fef61d8f",
    "reference": "10- Ephesians 6:10-18 \u201cPut on the whole armor of God\u201d",
    "question": "Many are the afflictions of the righteous: but the Lord ____ him out of them all.",
    "options": [
      "Heareth",
      "Heal",
      "Conceal",
      "Delivereth"
    ],
    "answer": "Delivereth",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0f7c2ad1-b253-464d-9905-6d7358cfa037",
    "reference": "10- Ephesians 6:10-18 \u201cPut on the whole armor of God\u201d",
    "question": "Servants, be ____ to them that are your masters according to the flesh, with fear and trembling....",
    "options": [
      "Kind",
      "Supportive",
      "Obedient",
      "Pray"
    ],
    "answer": "Obedient",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "be83008b-93dd-4cbd-84ff-d93f39c19921",
    "reference": "10- Ephesians 6:10-18 \u201cPut on the whole armor of God\u201d",
    "question": "What must one put on to stand against wiles of the devil?",
    "options": [
      "Whole armour of God",
      "Clean clothes",
      "Veil",
      "Nothing"
    ],
    "answer": "Whole armour of God",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4f441afa-c6d1-4637-84f9-71ee3ff62cec",
    "reference": "11- 2 Timothy 1:7 \u201cGod has not given us a spirit of fear\u201d",
    "question": "What are Christians wrestle against?",
    "options": [
      "The devil",
      "The flesh",
      "The blood",
      "Principalities"
    ],
    "answer": "Principalities",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "16388b45-562f-4012-ba45-6639f0697a89",
    "reference": "11- 2 Timothy 1:7 \u201cGod has not given us a spirit of fear\u201d",
    "question": "What spirit has God given us?",
    "options": [
      "Power",
      "Fear",
      "Love",
      "Sound mind",
      "a c & d"
    ],
    "answer": "a c & d",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "69323de9-888d-4093-a39e-f069b2a29ee2",
    "reference": "11- 2 Timothy 1:7 \u201cGod has not given us a spirit of fear\u201d",
    "question": "Whereunto I am appointed a ____, and apostle, and a teacher of the Gentiles.",
    "options": [
      "Son",
      "Believer",
      "Preacher",
      "Servant"
    ],
    "answer": "Preacher",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0268a944-e9cf-4e3a-975e-d3c9ba28664a",
    "reference": "12- Psalm 31:7 \u201cYou have known my soul in adversities\u201d",
    "question": "Hold fast the form of Sound ___, which thou hast heard of me, in faith and love which is in Christ Jesus",
    "options": [
      "Experience",
      "Teaching",
      "Words",
      "Hope"
    ],
    "answer": "Words",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "97201adf-ab50-4b50-90fd-d9b584209fe2",
    "reference": "12- Psalm 31:7 \u201cYou have known my soul in adversities\u201d",
    "question": "Into thine hand I commit my spirit: thou hast ____ me, O Lord God of truth.",
    "options": [
      "Forgiven",
      "Heard",
      "Redeemed",
      "Ignored"
    ],
    "answer": "Redeemed",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ec22688c-ba50-43b7-b989-1ae286d8d8f0",
    "reference": "12- Psalm 31:7 \u201cYou have known my soul in adversities\u201d",
    "question": "For thou art my ____ and my fortress; therefore for thy name's sake lead me, and guide me.",
    "options": [
      "Strength",
      "Redeemer",
      "Rock",
      "Lord"
    ],
    "answer": "Rock",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d09ea09c-018d-4743-ba15-57d18d3b49c4",
    "reference": "12- Psalm 31:7 \u201cYou have known my soul in adversities\u201d",
    "question": "In thee, O Lord, do I put my trust; let me never be ashamed: ___ me in thy righteousness",
    "options": [
      "Protect",
      "Help",
      "Forgive",
      "Deliver"
    ],
    "answer": "Deliver",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "16c09f3b-e667-410e-a1ac-f7eb45368ca2",
    "reference": "12- Psalm 31:7 \u201cYou have known my soul in adversities\u201d",
    "question": "Now know that the Lord ____ his anointed; he will hear him from his holy heaven with the saving strength of his right hand.",
    "options": [
      "Prepare",
      "Bless",
      "Ordain",
      "Saveth"
    ],
    "answer": "Saveth",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0b4c3e5b-ceef-4b13-8fa3-c2389e7556b2",
    "reference": "12- Psalm 31:7 \u201cYou have known my soul in adversities\u201d",
    "question": "We will rejoice in thy ____, and in the name of our God we will set up our banners: the Lord fulfil all thy petitions.",
    "options": [
      "Salvation",
      "Grace",
      "Mercy",
      "Love"
    ],
    "answer": "Salvation",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3c74c95a-2704-46af-94a4-903b41b4b1d0",
    "reference": "14- Psalm 6:2 \u201cHave mercy on me\u201d",
    "question": "Let the words of my mouth, and the meditation of my heart, be acceptable in thy sight, O Lord, my ___, and redeemer.",
    "options": [
      "King",
      "Savior",
      "Father",
      "Strength"
    ],
    "answer": "Strength",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "41668485-c6dd-41f4-ad6b-721d3ba122d4",
    "reference": "14- Psalm 6:2 \u201cHave mercy on me\u201d",
    "question": "O Lord, ____ me not in thine anger, neither chasten me in thy hot displeasure.",
    "options": [
      "Forget",
      "Abandon",
      "Rebuke",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Rebuke",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "083355f0-0ce3-481a-9814-edc803d53868",
    "reference": "14- Psalm 6:2 \u201cHave mercy on me\u201d",
    "question": "For thou, Lord, wilt ____ the righteous; with favour wilt thou compass him as with a shield.",
    "options": [
      "Bless",
      "Honor",
      "Remember",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Bless",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b71ffd0e-ce51-4393-a9ec-2efbdd549619",
    "reference": "14- Psalm 6:2 \u201cHave mercy on me\u201d",
    "question": "Return, O Lord, __ my soul: oh save me for thy mercies' sake.",
    "options": [
      "Remember",
      "Trust",
      "Bless",
      "Deliver"
    ],
    "answer": "Deliver",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9a060d11-12ee-4e4e-ab14-5f74ad6ebe87",
    "reference": "14- Psalm 6:2 \u201cHave mercy on me\u201d",
    "question": "He shall call upon me, and I will ____ him: I will be with him in trouble; I will deliver him, and honour him.",
    "options": [
      "Answer",
      "Remember",
      "Bless",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Answer",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "636886e2-fdfc-4390-acdc-aaebffc8a7b2",
    "reference": "16- Psalm 105:15 \u201cDo not touch My anointed ones, and do My prophets no harm\u201d",
    "question": "Thou shalt not be ____ for the terror by night; nor for the arrow that flieth by day;",
    "options": [
      "Seen",
      "Moved",
      "Rebuked",
      "Afraid"
    ],
    "answer": "Afraid",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7a022477-a889-4f13-af64-d38b1075598b",
    "reference": "16- Psalm 105:15 \u201cDo not touch My anointed ones, and do My prophets no harm\u201d",
    "question": "O give ____ unto the Lord; call upon his name: make known his deeds among the people",
    "options": [
      "Praise",
      "A shout of joy",
      "Thanks",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Thanks",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6f09b4a3-d03a-4cd6-82bb-1279f0579429",
    "reference": "16- Psalm 105:15 \u201cDo not touch My anointed ones, and do My prophets no harm\u201d",
    "question": "___ ye in his holy name: let the heart of them rejoice that seek the Lord",
    "options": [
      "Bless",
      "Honor",
      "Glory",
      "Praise"
    ],
    "answer": "Glory",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8d01bcdc-6b99-4f82-8717-a8d7af7ef97b",
    "reference": "16- Psalm 105:15 \u201cDo not touch My anointed ones, and do My prophets no harm\u201d",
    "question": "And he ____ his people greatly; and made them stronger than their enemies",
    "options": [
      "Increased",
      "Punished",
      "Forgot",
      "Saved"
    ],
    "answer": "Increased",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8ddba81a-955f-47c3-aad3-8f5b86fd8d93",
    "reference": "16- Psalm 105:15 \u201cDo not touch My anointed ones, and do My prophets no harm\u201d",
    "question": "When mine enemies are turned back, they shall fall and ____ at thy presence.",
    "options": [
      "Worship",
      "Perish",
      "Repent",
      "Cry out"
    ],
    "answer": "Perish",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "caa70654-99c5-4a6e-a0c1-c866e33fe156",
    "reference": "16- Psalm 105:15 \u201cDo not touch My anointed ones, and do My prophets no harm\u201d",
    "question": "And they that ___ thy name will put their trust in thee: for thou, Lord hast not forsaken them that seek thee.",
    "options": [
      "Believe",
      "Rely on",
      "Seek",
      "Know"
    ],
    "answer": "Know",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6081f652-7e79-4dca-a7a3-655340557309",
    "reference": "18- Matthew 5:1-14 The Beatitudes",
    "question": "The Lord is known by the ____ which he executeth: the wicked is snared in the work of his own hands.",
    "options": [
      "Power",
      "Judgment",
      "Love",
      "Worthiness"
    ],
    "answer": "Judgment",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4bf4b27d-0b57-46f5-b7f7-9c2da2a7e803",
    "reference": "18- Matthew 5:1-14 The Beatitudes",
    "question": "Blessed are they they which do hunger and thirst after ____: for they shall be filled.",
    "options": [
      "Righteousness",
      "Peace",
      "Reconciliation",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Righteousness",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "682b2d14-b142-4f1c-a9bd-5cf357d5fa98",
    "reference": "18- Matthew 5:1-14 The Beatitudes",
    "question": "Ye are the ____ of the world. A city that is set on an hill cannot be hid.",
    "options": [
      "Joy",
      "The way",
      "Salt",
      "Light"
    ],
    "answer": "Light",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f99dfeca-97bf-4ab5-9938-b35d6c0bdc0f",
    "reference": "19- Matthew 9:29 \u201cAccording to your faith let it be to you\u201d",
    "question": "Blessed are the peacemakers: for they shall be called the ___ of God.",
    "options": [
      "Redeemed",
      "Favorites",
      "Children",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Children",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4adf879f-1fe1-4643-8e51-9050d62c6a6f",
    "reference": "19- Matthew 9:29 \u201cAccording to your faith let it be to you\u201d",
    "question": "In Matthew 9 the woman who touched Jesus had an issue of Blood for how long?",
    "options": [
      "7 years",
      "12 years",
      "It is not clear",
      "12 months"
    ],
    "answer": "12 years",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6993ca00-5241-4406-b1d9-d59d00a52338",
    "reference": "19- Matthew 9:29 \u201cAccording to your faith let it be to you\u201d",
    "question": "And When Jesus departed thence, two ____ men followed him, crying, and saying, Thou Son of David, have mercy on us.",
    "options": [
      "Blind",
      "Righteous",
      "Holy",
      "Poor"
    ],
    "answer": "Blind",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "bf6efc60-9ed2-4d9b-b65a-bc30abad4325",
    "reference": "20- Matthew 9:37-38 \u201cThe harvest truly is plentiful, but the laborers are few\u201d",
    "question": "Then saith he unto his disciples, The harvest truly is plenteous, but the ____ are few;",
    "options": [
      "Workers",
      "Believers",
      "Sinners",
      "Laborers"
    ],
    "answer": "Laborers",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8b9f4857-dda0-4417-a429-7e12eb6ae044",
    "reference": "20- Matthew 9:37-38 \u201cThe harvest truly is plentiful, but the laborers are few\u201d",
    "question": "And as ye go, preach, saying, The ____ of heaven is at hand.",
    "options": [
      "Fire",
      "Son",
      "Kingdom",
      "Redeemed"
    ],
    "answer": "Kingdom",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3b015a65-9470-467d-804b-7e69e1dac18f",
    "reference": "21- Matthew 12:33-37 \u201cA tree is known by its fruit\u201d",
    "question": "What is the other name of Simon?",
    "options": [
      "Andrew",
      "Thomas",
      "Isaiah",
      "Peter"
    ],
    "answer": "Peter",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f773ca8a-151a-4b54-81c2-d31df2f88d2a",
    "reference": "21- Matthew 12:33-37 \u201cA tree is known by its fruit\u201d",
    "question": "Either make the tree ___, and his fruit good; or else make the tree corrupt, and his fruit corrupt: for the tree is known by his fruit.",
    "options": [
      "Good",
      "Great",
      "A blessing",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Good",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7f1121cf-93d3-4249-8626-388498a8e75b",
    "reference": "21- Matthew 12:33-37 \u201cA tree is known by its fruit\u201d",
    "question": "He that is not with me is ____ me; and he that gathereth not with me scattereth abroad.",
    "options": [
      "Fighting",
      "Follows",
      "Without",
      "Against"
    ],
    "answer": "Against",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d2802d08-bb68-4202-b9bf-e59935e8d1fb",
    "reference": "22- Matthew 13:1-13 Parable of the Sower",
    "question": "For by thy words thou shalt be ____, and by thy words thou shalt be condemned.",
    "options": [
      "Justified",
      "Judged",
      "Reconciled",
      "Rescued"
    ],
    "answer": "Justified",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7a2ea862-b433-4075-9124-74cf3364d31d",
    "reference": "22- Matthew 13:1-13 Parable of the Sower",
    "question": "Why does Jesus speak in Parable?",
    "options": [
      "So that only the chosen one may understand",
      "Because he can",
      "Because God commission him to",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "So that only the chosen one may understand",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f06e5aa3-af35-4c93-8ac6-307149176c80",
    "reference": "22- Matthew 13:1-13 Parable of the Sower",
    "question": "Who hath ears to hear, let him ____.",
    "options": [
      "Seek",
      "Listen",
      "Understand",
      "Hear"
    ],
    "answer": "Hear",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "91ab001d-a4a8-4ffa-8027-a43c62e867fa",
    "reference": "23- Matthew 13: 14-53 The Kingdom of Heaven",
    "question": "But ___ are your eyes, for they see: and your ears, for they hear.",
    "options": [
      "Great",
      "Sufficient",
      "Courageous",
      "Blessed"
    ],
    "answer": "Blessed",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3bd13cbd-4f02-4183-a18d-264f8c3381e9",
    "reference": "23- Matthew 13: 14-53 The Kingdom of Heaven",
    "question": "The field is the ____; the good seed are the children of the kingdom; but the tares are the children of the wicked one;",
    "options": [
      "World",
      "Hearts of men",
      "Earth",
      "a & c"
    ],
    "answer": "World",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8fe150c8-eff5-4bab-be41-1ac1d48c27ba",
    "reference": "23- Matthew 13: 14-53 The Kingdom of Heaven",
    "question": "And shall cast them into a furnace of ___: there shall be wailing and gnashing of teeth.",
    "options": [
      "Blessings",
      "Love",
      "Fire",
      "The world"
    ],
    "answer": "Fire",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b2de5ba5-be70-4c3e-9aeb-4df654f94c3e",
    "reference": "24- Romans 8:37 \u201cWe are more than conquerors\u201d",
    "question": "Is not this the ____ son? Is not his mother called Mary?",
    "options": [
      "Lord's",
      "Farmer's",
      "Carpenter's",
      "Father's"
    ],
    "answer": "Carpenter's",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b10ee2d8-5c3b-4cb6-94d0-699749834219",
    "reference": "24- Romans 8:37 \u201cWe are more than conquerors\u201d",
    "question": "What shall we then say to these things? If God be for us, who ___ be against us?",
    "options": [
      "Will",
      "might",
      "Can",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Can",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d3f11c0a-1a0f-489a-b2e1-b297369df29a",
    "reference": "24- Romans 8:37 \u201cWe are more than conquerors\u201d",
    "question": "Who shall separate us from the love of Christ?",
    "options": [
      "Nothing",
      "Tribulation",
      "Distress",
      "Famine"
    ],
    "answer": "Nothing",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "49f3d065-e08e-4a4d-91af-8ae7ad39c988",
    "reference": "25- Romans 6:17-20 Servants of Righteousness Freed from Sin",
    "question": "And we know that all things work together for good to them that ____ God, to them who are called according to his purpose.",
    "options": [
      "Believe",
      "Love",
      "Call to",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Love",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "29caf0c0-8976-463f-b193-cd1b30eaca57",
    "reference": "25- Romans 6:17-20 Servants of Righteousness Freed from Sin",
    "question": "For sin shall not have ____ over you; for ye are not under the law, but under grace.",
    "options": [
      "Effect",
      "Stronghold",
      "Dominion",
      "Power"
    ],
    "answer": "Dominion",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "dcb9ebcc-b436-430b-945a-ff9de9b6173f",
    "reference": "25- Romans 6:17-20 Servants of Righteousness Freed from Sin",
    "question": "Being then made free from sin, ye became the servants of ____.",
    "options": [
      "Sins",
      "Love",
      "The Lord",
      "Righteousness"
    ],
    "answer": "Righteousness",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "358ff168-b9a3-4cc0-a09c-0bd32357067a",
    "reference": "26- John 16:13 \u201cThe Spirit of truth \u2026 will guide you\u201d",
    "question": "What is the wages of sin?",
    "options": [
      "Nothing",
      "Compassion",
      "Life's sentence",
      "Death"
    ],
    "answer": "Death",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "250ce122-c63e-4bd0-b734-1da11fdaf205",
    "reference": "26- John 16:13 \u201cThe Spirit of truth \u2026 will guide you\u201d",
    "question": "What is the Spirit of truth?",
    "options": [
      "The gift Christians receive from God",
      "The Word of God",
      "The Holy Spirit",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "The Holy Spirit",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0ccd34f5-3a5f-4443-a0b0-e127a269112f",
    "reference": "26- John 16:13 \u201cThe Spirit of truth \u2026 will guide you\u201d",
    "question": "Yea, the time cometh, that whosoever killeth you will think that he ___ God service.",
    "options": [
      "Renders",
      "Provides",
      "Supports",
      "Doeth"
    ],
    "answer": "Doeth",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "822d2931-599c-46d8-8c0b-eceee163ee21",
    "reference": "27- 1 Peter 5:7 \u201cCasting all your care upon Him\u201d",
    "question": "All things that the Father hath are ____: therefore said I, that he shall take of mine, and shall shew it unto you.",
    "options": [
      "Ours",
      "Great",
      "Blessed",
      "Mine"
    ],
    "answer": "Mine",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "db78c3fb-1c3d-4e19-b74b-c697eb9fe930",
    "reference": "27- 1 Peter 5:7 \u201cCasting all your care upon Him\u201d",
    "question": "Why must you cast your care upon Him?",
    "options": [
      "Because he loves you",
      "Because he saved you",
      "Because he is the king",
      "Because he careth for you"
    ],
    "answer": "Because he careth for you",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f7f3ddab-8687-4d94-918a-efbfd433eae6",
    "reference": "27- 1 Peter 5:7 \u201cCasting all your care upon Him\u201d",
    "question": "And when the chief Shepherd shall appear, ye shall receive a ____ of glory that fadeth not away.",
    "options": [
      "Trophy",
      "Crown",
      "Prize",
      "Throne"
    ],
    "answer": "Crown",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "90963710-c937-46fb-b428-db53b9739533",
    "reference": "28- Romans 12:2 \u201cBe transformed by the renewing of your mind\u201d",
    "question": "Be sober; be ___; because your adversary the devil, as a roaring lion, walketh about, seeking whom he may devour:",
    "options": [
      "Strong",
      "Courageous",
      "Vigilant",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Vigilant",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e0c50a5f-675f-40d9-9bb7-8df8233d450c",
    "reference": "28- Romans 12:2 \u201cBe transformed by the renewing of your mind\u201d",
    "question": "So we, being many, are ___ body in Christ, and every one members one of another.",
    "options": [
      "Unified",
      "Blessed",
      "One",
      "Conquerors"
    ],
    "answer": "One",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "efb8b417-883e-45a1-93cf-f25825c3459b",
    "reference": "29- 1 Thessalonians 5:16-18 \u201cPray without ceasing\u201d",
    "question": "Rejoicing in ____; patient in tribulation; continuing instant in prayer;",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Kindness",
      "Hope",
      "Prayers"
    ],
    "answer": "Hope",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1c761101-e553-4585-a12a-632021bd2ad7",
    "reference": "29- 1 Thessalonians 5:16-18 \u201cPray without ceasing\u201d",
    "question": "In what circumstances must we give thanks to God?",
    "options": [
      "On thanksgiving",
      "All the times",
      "When God bless us",
      "When we feel like it"
    ],
    "answer": "All the times",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "88342271-5236-4ec0-a77b-61e226aa5d90",
    "reference": "30- Nehemiah 8:10 \u201cThe joy of the Lord is your strength\u201d",
    "question": "For God hath not appointed us to wrath, but to obtain ____ by our Lord Jesus Christ,",
    "options": [
      "Grace",
      "Gifts",
      "Mercies",
      "Salvation"
    ],
    "answer": "Salvation",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c7d1ebb3-0db2-4531-bc93-831c92eeb4c4",
    "reference": "30- Nehemiah 8:10 \u201cThe joy of the Lord is your strength\u201d",
    "question": "When did Ezra bring the law before the congregation?",
    "options": [
      "The second day of the sixth month",
      "The first day of the fifth month",
      "The first day of the seventh month",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "The first day of the seventh month",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ad206d62-c058-40a0-b852-2b262993fb1c",
    "reference": "31- 2 Corinthians 5:17 \u201cIf anyone is in Christ he is a new creation\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Ezra?",
    "options": [
      "A preacher",
      "A teacher",
      "The Tirshatha",
      "The priest"
    ],
    "answer": "The priest",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "816289db-dad2-4f95-af11-8ff30e9092e1",
    "reference": "31- 2 Corinthians 5:17 \u201cIf anyone is in Christ he is a new creation\u201d",
    "question": "Now then we are ____ for Christ, as though God did beseech you by us: we pray you in Christ's stead, be ye reconciled to God.",
    "options": [
      "Servants",
      "Priests",
      "Ambassadors",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Ambassadors",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2daa9279-b94b-41bd-90b3-90b9d5ede235",
    "reference": "31- 2 Corinthians 5:17 \u201cIf anyone is in Christ he is a new creation\u201d",
    "question": "For we walk by ___, not by sight:",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Wisdom",
      "Faith",
      "Understanding"
    ],
    "answer": "Faith",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fb90c078-b303-4dbe-bc78-f011f92d3785",
    "reference": "31- 2 Corinthians 5:17 \u201cIf anyone is in Christ he is a new creation\u201d",
    "question": "And ___ things are of God, who hath reconciled us to himself by Jesus Christ, and hath given to us the ministry of reconciliation;",
    "options": [
      "All",
      "Blessed",
      "Favorable",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2e68fbb0-559a-4f7e-aa58-82815e18a0f0",
    "reference": "1- Jeremiah 29:11 \u201cI know the thoughts that I think toward you\u201d",
    "question": "And seek the peace of the city whither I have caused you to be carried away captives, and ____ unto the Lord for it:",
    "options": [
      "Ask",
      "Beg",
      "Seek",
      "Pray"
    ],
    "answer": "Pray",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4f709963-54ef-40d6-8cad-cec5e769a901",
    "reference": "1- Jeremiah 29:11 \u201cI know the thoughts that I think toward you\u201d",
    "question": "And ye shall ____ me, and find me, when ye shall search for me with all your heart.",
    "options": [
      "See",
      "Seek",
      "Praise",
      "Offer"
    ],
    "answer": "Seek",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fe055a07-a7a1-4373-921a-4ca4c3fdc83f",
    "reference": "2- Psalm 30:5 \u201cJoy comes in the morning\u201d",
    "question": "What are the thoughts that the Lord think toward you?",
    "options": [
      "Compassion",
      "Love",
      "Redemption",
      "Peace"
    ],
    "answer": "Peace",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "29c5d541-1b6d-4f31-b744-c40c4be14310",
    "reference": "2- Psalm 30:5 \u201cJoy comes in the morning\u201d",
    "question": "O Lord my God, I ____ unto thee, and thou hast healed me.",
    "options": [
      "Smile",
      "Pray",
      "Cried",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Cried",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7fc45ed7-3115-424e-a232-d0056c31ca64",
    "reference": "2- Psalm 30:5 \u201cJoy comes in the morning\u201d",
    "question": "Hear, O Lord, and have ____ upon me: Lord, be thou my helper.",
    "options": [
      "Pity",
      "Love",
      "Blessing",
      "Mercy"
    ],
    "answer": "Mercy",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3b2dc95e-302a-4407-8eff-5f539307dc9c",
    "reference": "3- Deuteronomy 28:1-13  Benefits of Obedience",
    "question": "____ unto the Lord, O ye saints of his, and give thanks at the remembrance of his holiness.",
    "options": [
      "Praise",
      "Worship",
      "Sing",
      "Cry"
    ],
    "answer": "Sing",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c20c78aa-1bad-4c97-8578-5588fac527fc",
    "reference": "3- Deuteronomy 28:1-13  Benefits of Obedience",
    "question": "The Lord shall ____ thee an holy people unto himself, as he hath sworn unto thee, if thou shalt keep the commandments of the Lord thy God and walk in his ways.",
    "options": [
      "Favor",
      "Forgive",
      "Punish",
      "Establish"
    ],
    "answer": "Establish",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "557ae81d-90fb-4869-990f-4ad3277499ae",
    "reference": "4- Deuteronomy 28: 15-58 Consequences of Disobedience",
    "question": "How many of God commandments are his children expected to obey?",
    "options": [
      "Ten",
      "One",
      "It is not clear",
      "All"
    ],
    "answer": "All",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "76ff773c-ca32-47a2-8a7d-37baf27259d4",
    "reference": "4- Deuteronomy 28: 15-58 Consequences of Disobedience",
    "question": "____ shalt be the fruit of thy body, and the fruit  of thy land, the increase of thy kine, and the flocks of thy sheep.",
    "options": [
      "Juicy",
      "Sweet",
      "Bitter",
      "Cursed"
    ],
    "answer": "Cursed",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "93450286-9344-4e6d-9b1b-1c21f5cdc50c",
    "reference": "4- Deuteronomy 28: 15-58 Consequences of Disobedience",
    "question": "All thy trees and fruit of thy land shall the ____ consume.",
    "options": [
      "Lord",
      "Devil",
      "Locust",
      "Criminals"
    ],
    "answer": "Locust",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7f19a53f-dc8d-453b-93e5-1d83c696d0cb",
    "reference": "5- John 15: 1-5 \u201cLet not your heart be troubled\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord shall smite thee in the knees, and in the legs, with a sore botch that cannot be ___, from the sole of thy foot unto the top of thy head.",
    "options": [
      "Seen",
      "Healed",
      "Understood",
      "Bearable"
    ],
    "answer": "Healed",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6b96e640-d63c-44e5-962a-c883a9284496",
    "reference": "5- John 15: 1-5 \u201cLet not your heart be troubled\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the true vine?",
    "options": [
      "Nicodemus",
      "Jesus",
      "John",
      "God"
    ],
    "answer": "Jesus",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c3de664d-4c94-4119-8593-43c9bdf8c853",
    "reference": "5- John 15: 1-5 \u201cLet not your heart be troubled\u201d",
    "question": "What must we do to bear much fruit?",
    "options": [
      "Work hard",
      "Be obedient",
      "Abide in Jesus",
      "Sin no more"
    ],
    "answer": "Abide in Jesus",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f0ddd8e5-c2d5-4314-afd7-c5e2d02363e6",
    "reference": "6- John 14:6 \u201c[Jesus is] the way, the truth, and the life\u201d",
    "question": "But that the world may know that I ____ the Father; and as the Father gave me commandment, even so I do. Arise, let us go hence.",
    "options": [
      "Am",
      "Love",
      "Was with",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Love",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6f341425-0b8d-48c2-b8e6-61b0d56170fa",
    "reference": "6- John 14:6 \u201c[Jesus is] the way, the truth, and the life\u201d",
    "question": "Let not your heart be troubled: ye believe in God, believe also in ____.",
    "options": [
      "John",
      "Israel",
      "Me",
      "No one"
    ],
    "answer": "Me",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "eee53d0a-1de7-422d-b352-8bc53ed0a652",
    "reference": "7- Isaiah 26:3 \u201cYou will keep him in perfect peace\u201d",
    "question": "Who asked Jesus to show him the Father?",
    "options": [
      "John",
      "Thomas",
      "Philip",
      "Jeremiah"
    ],
    "answer": "Philip",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3318cec2-c3d1-42f1-8e7c-fcc12d3b0795",
    "reference": "7- Isaiah 26:3 \u201cYou will keep him in perfect peace\u201d",
    "question": "Lord, thou wilt ordain ___ for us: for thou also hast wrought all our works in us.",
    "options": [
      "Knowledge",
      "Education",
      "Intelligence",
      "Peace"
    ],
    "answer": "Peace",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "386e523c-40b3-4a58-8b03-b12618623d96",
    "reference": "7- Isaiah 26:3 \u201cYou will keep him in perfect peace\u201d",
    "question": "The way of the ____ is uprightness: thou, most upright, dost weigh the path of the just.",
    "options": [
      "Kind",
      "Meek",
      "Just",
      "Christian"
    ],
    "answer": "Just",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0887046d-d77f-4b71-9a95-f3abe286d4e5",
    "reference": "8- Joshua 1:8 \u201cYou shall meditate in [this Book of the Law]\u201d",
    "question": "Open ye the ____, that the righteous nation which keepeth the truth may enter in.",
    "options": [
      "Mind",
      "Gates",
      "Way",
      "House"
    ],
    "answer": "Gates",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "adc12b78-53c1-4d78-8753-735b2feed430",
    "reference": "8- Joshua 1:8 \u201cYou shall meditate in [this Book of the Law]\u201d",
    "question": "Be ___ and of a good courage: for unto this people shalt thou divide for an inheritance the land, which I sware unto their fathers to give them.",
    "options": [
      "Nice",
      "Strong",
      "Faithful",
      "Vigilant"
    ],
    "answer": "Strong",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "45f96bbc-a573-4b09-8867-dbe7492b29f7",
    "reference": "9- Proverbs 3:13 \u201cHappy is the man who finds wisdom\u201d",
    "question": "Whoever he be that doth rebel against thy _____, and will not hearken unto thy words in all that thou commandest him, he shall be put to death: only be strong and of a good courage.",
    "options": [
      "Commandment",
      "Words",
      "Love",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Commandment",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "01590785-fa50-4d50-b999-f343647a27ed",
    "reference": "9- Proverbs 3:13 \u201cHappy is the man who finds wisdom\u201d",
    "question": "In all thy _____ acknowledge him, and he shall direct thy paths.",
    "options": [
      "Power",
      "Thoughts",
      "Life",
      "Ways"
    ],
    "answer": "Ways",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "344a17d8-5e2c-4a8e-b1c6-a9e87e06ffd0",
    "reference": "9- Proverbs 3:13 \u201cHappy is the man who finds wisdom\u201d",
    "question": "The ____ of the Lord is in the house of the wicked: but he blesseth the habitation of the just.",
    "options": [
      "Mirror",
      "Supply",
      "Gifts",
      "Curse"
    ],
    "answer": "Curse",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "099fa40f-7b37-4417-b774-79b917508008",
    "reference": "10- Proverbs 3:5-6 \u201cTrust in the Lord with all your heart\u201d",
    "question": "Trust in the Lord with all thine ___; and lean not unto thine own understanding.",
    "options": [
      "Mind",
      "Money",
      "Heart",
      "Body"
    ],
    "answer": "Heart",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "399e79f7-59da-4c1d-b780-afdb34cf7bed",
    "reference": "10- Proverbs 3:5-6 \u201cTrust in the Lord with all your heart\u201d",
    "question": "For the Lord shall be thy ____, and shall keep thy foot from being taken.",
    "options": [
      "Helper",
      "Provider",
      "Confidence",
      "Redeemer"
    ],
    "answer": "Confidence",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "04964f49-5327-4cab-aa56-a87b600aeb5c",
    "reference": "10- Proverbs 3:5-6 \u201cTrust in the Lord with all your heart\u201d",
    "question": "My son, forget not my law; but let thine ____ keep my commandments;",
    "options": [
      "Heart",
      "Mind",
      "Children",
      "Parents"
    ],
    "answer": "Heart",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7214f752-8aba-491d-b9fa-05d46ecb79e7",
    "reference": "11- Proverbs 31:30 \u201cA woman who fears the Lord\u201d",
    "question": "Be not ___ in thine own eyes: fear the Lord, and depart from evil.",
    "options": [
      "Rude",
      "Shy",
      "Wise",
      "Afraid"
    ],
    "answer": "Wise",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "741f4f13-d636-4b5e-8f88-f9fae2c64ac4",
    "reference": "11- Proverbs 31:30 \u201cA woman who fears the Lord\u201d",
    "question": "What can find a ___ woman?",
    "options": [
      "Famous",
      "Knowledgeable",
      "Virtuous",
      "Wealthy"
    ],
    "answer": "Virtuous",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "be24cc25-476c-490c-af46-f0bdaad163e7",
    "reference": "12- Joshua 1:5 \u201cI will not leave you nor forsake you\u201d",
    "question": "Give not thy ____ unto women, nor thy ways to that which destroyeth kings",
    "options": [
      "Heart",
      "Love",
      "Strength",
      "Money"
    ],
    "answer": "Strength",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "934c0a15-b144-4031-b521-df2a7d8e4964",
    "reference": "12- Joshua 1:5 \u201cI will not leave you nor forsake you\u201d",
    "question": "Every ___ that the sole of your foot shall tread upon, that have I given unto you, as I said unto Moses",
    "options": [
      "Neighborhood",
      "Nation",
      "Place",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Place",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a9744476-e6ea-433c-9816-85302b2e4261",
    "reference": "13- Philippians 4:8 Meditate on Things of Virtue",
    "question": "Have not I ____ thee? Be strong and of a good courage; be not afraid, neither be thou disnayed",
    "options": [
      "Called",
      "Consecrated",
      "Commended",
      "Trusted"
    ],
    "answer": "Commended",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4a8a069b-6a98-4bd3-b89b-a15d7c8ba74b",
    "reference": "13- Philippians 4:8 Meditate on Things of Virtue",
    "question": "____ in Lord always: and again I say, ____.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Trust",
      "Be braved",
      "Rejoice"
    ],
    "answer": "Rejoice",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b204b6f4-ebe4-4615-84af-16a128a4bfe7",
    "reference": "13- Philippians 4:8 Meditate on Things of Virtue",
    "question": "For our _____ is in heaven: from whence also we look for the Savior, the Lord Jesus Christ:",
    "options": [
      "Conversation",
      "Home",
      "Blessings",
      "Father"
    ],
    "answer": "Conversation",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ced01e63-5ed5-4eca-a9f8-08cbe77b3712",
    "reference": "14- 2 Corinthians 10:5-6 \u201cCasting down arguments\u201d",
    "question": "And the ____ of God, which passeth all understanding, shall keep your hearts and minds through Christ Jesus.",
    "options": [
      "Wisdom",
      "Peace",
      "Love",
      "Thoughts"
    ],
    "answer": "Peace",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c677d1c6-98c4-49d2-8eb8-f743c9f3a64f",
    "reference": "14- 2 Corinthians 10:5-6 \u201cCasting down arguments\u201d",
    "question": "For the weapons of our warfare are not ____, but mighty through God to the pulling down of strong holds;",
    "options": [
      "Evil",
      "Guns",
      "Carnal",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Carnal",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6fa77c79-d262-40c2-99e5-bfc48da04342",
    "reference": "14- 2 Corinthians 10:5-6 \u201cCasting down arguments\u201d",
    "question": "But we will not ____ of things without our measure, but according to the measure of the rule which God hath distributed to us, a measure to reach even unto you.",
    "options": [
      "Boast",
      "Complain",
      "Wish",
      "Discuss"
    ],
    "answer": "Boast",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9a7247b3-0e6f-4d8f-b220-207c6030c938",
    "reference": "14- 2 Corinthians 10:5-6 \u201cCasting down arguments\u201d",
    "question": "For we know in part, and we ___ in part.",
    "options": [
      "Prophesy",
      "Wish",
      "Confess",
      "Talk"
    ],
    "answer": "Prophesy",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "30dc5c11-0789-4656-b838-a6124e7c0261",
    "reference": "16- 2 Corinthians 9:7 \u201cGod loves a cheerful giver\u201d",
    "question": "And though I bestow all my goods to feed the poor, and though I give my body to be burned, and have not ___, it profiteth me nothing.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Compassion",
      "Ambition",
      "Charity"
    ],
    "answer": "Charity",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5d54417c-250d-4986-8183-99a3c946372b",
    "reference": "16- 2 Corinthians 9:7 \u201cGod loves a cheerful giver\u201d",
    "question": "And God is able to make all ___ abound toward you; that ye, always having all sufficiency in all things, may abound to every good work:",
    "options": [
      "Gifts",
      "Wisdom",
      "Grace",
      "Peace"
    ],
    "answer": "Grace",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "62b9211f-c7b8-426e-bdd4-7759e8b834d7",
    "reference": "17- 2 Corinthians 9:8 \u201cHaving all sufficiency in all things\u201d",
    "question": "And by their ___ for you, which long after you for the exceeding grace of God in you.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Forbearance",
      "Prayer",
      "Provision"
    ],
    "answer": "Prayer",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "69b28028-054e-407e-86f9-a82fa3771037",
    "reference": "17- 2 Corinthians 9:8 \u201cHaving all sufficiency in all things\u201d",
    "question": "Being enriched in every thing to all ____, which causeth through us thanksgiving to God.",
    "options": [
      "Bountifulness",
      "Praise",
      "Gifts",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Bountifulness",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f811f1f2-2746-4afe-a3f0-93cb089ade6b",
    "reference": "18- Romans 6:23 \u201cThe wages of sin is death\u201d",
    "question": "He which soweth bountifully shall reap?",
    "options": [
      "Surely",
      "Admirably",
      "Wonderfully",
      "Bountifully"
    ],
    "answer": "Bountifully",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b77ad6a5-e9c4-4c63-9945-7413b8432a64",
    "reference": "18- Romans 6:23 \u201cThe wages of sin is death\u201d",
    "question": "For when ye were the ____ of sin, ye were free from righteousness.",
    "options": [
      "Servants",
      "Friends",
      "Kings",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Servants",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9fec3fd5-6677-438c-a778-f120f6303cdd",
    "reference": "18- Romans 6:23 \u201cThe wages of sin is death\u201d",
    "question": "For __ shall not have dominion over you: for ye are not under the law, but under grace.",
    "options": [
      "Grace",
      "Sin",
      "Self pity",
      "Curse"
    ],
    "answer": "Sin",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "43b1d7ca-3e2c-4bad-8155-9c1d99656e12",
    "reference": "19- Romans 8:1 \u201cNo condemnation to those who are in Christ\u201d",
    "question": "Knowing that Christ being ___ from the dead dieth no more; death hath no more dominion over him.",
    "options": [
      "Relived",
      "Resurrected",
      "Raised",
      "Brought"
    ],
    "answer": "Raised",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d0d33daa-ade4-4225-aa51-833f82f88a27",
    "reference": "19- Romans 8:1 \u201cNo condemnation to those who are in Christ\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the author of Romans?",
    "options": [
      "Jesus",
      "Paul",
      "Matthew",
      "Philip"
    ],
    "answer": "Paul",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c6480f3a-2819-4d41-a6d3-44ff9552b7ea",
    "reference": "19- Romans 8:1 \u201cNo condemnation to those who are in Christ\u201d",
    "question": "That is, that I may be ____ together with you by the mutual faith both of you and me.",
    "options": [
      "comforted",
      "Saved",
      "Holy",
      "Presented"
    ],
    "answer": "comforted",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "da745973-512c-4bd6-b52a-e79dd28dac25",
    "reference": "20- Romans 8:11 \u201c[God] will also give life to your mortal bodies\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the author of Romans writing to?",
    "options": [
      "Christians in Rome",
      "Christians in Jerusalem",
      "Christians in Greece",
      "Christians in Philippi"
    ],
    "answer": "Christians in Rome",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "012e4c5a-66c4-47d0-b06d-a0d07e07c763",
    "reference": "20- Romans 8:11 \u201c[God] will also give life to your mortal bodies\u201d",
    "question": "How is the carnal mind towards God?",
    "options": [
      "Unloving",
      "Disrespectful",
      "Enmity",
      "Unkind"
    ],
    "answer": "Enmity",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "87af7cf1-a4a3-4bd1-bbd4-5a614845a049",
    "reference": "21- Galatians 2:20 \u201cNo longer I who live, but Christ lives in me\u201d",
    "question": "For the law of the ____ of life in Christ Jesus hath made me free from the law of sin and death",
    "options": [
      "Spirit",
      "Love",
      "Way",
      "Kingship"
    ],
    "answer": "Spirit",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "73cbac85-28fa-40ba-9714-df56f1ed15e9",
    "reference": "21- Galatians 2:20 \u201cNo longer I who live, but Christ lives in me\u201d",
    "question": "According to Paul (Galatians 2), is man justified by works?",
    "options": [
      "No",
      "Yes but only if it is good work",
      "Paul doesn't talk about justification",
      "It is not clear"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6143a87a-ec72-4abe-aa7d-fd67f9acbbba",
    "reference": "21- Galatians 2:20 \u201cNo longer I who live, but Christ lives in me\u201d",
    "question": "Are ye so foolish? Having begun in the Spirit, are ye now made perfect by the ____?",
    "options": [
      "Hard work",
      "Flesh",
      "Unbelief",
      "Obedience"
    ],
    "answer": "Flesh",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2992ad0f-02fb-4c98-8345-209a093a556d",
    "reference": "22- Galatians 3:13 \u201cChrist redeemed us from the curse of the law\u201d",
    "question": "Does righteousness comes by the law?",
    "options": [
      "Definitely",
      "It is not mentioned",
      "Depends if one truly follows the law",
      "No"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f47d87fd-d21c-4a07-b376-87f30791467c",
    "reference": "22- Galatians 3:13 \u201cChrist redeemed us from the curse of the law\u201d",
    "question": "Even as Abraham believed God, and it was accounted to him for ____",
    "options": [
      "Blessing",
      "Righteousness",
      "Favor",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Righteousness",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "69a762f7-5259-40de-afcf-133217827ecd",
    "reference": "22- Galatians 3:13 \u201cChrist redeemed us from the curse of the law\u201d",
    "question": "How must the just live?",
    "options": [
      "By hard work",
      "By obedience",
      "By faith",
      "By honesty"
    ],
    "answer": "By faith",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3371edc4-28ce-45ab-a04c-ca9a5e6a0c99",
    "reference": "23- Galatians 4:7 \u201cAn heir of God through Christ\u201d",
    "question": "How would the Gentiles' benefit from Abraham blessing?",
    "options": [
      "Through civilization",
      "Through globalization",
      "Through the Holy Spirit",
      "Through Jesus Christ"
    ],
    "answer": "Through Jesus Christ",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5fa2e838-450d-4c9d-8325-cfbf7eb35179",
    "reference": "23- Galatians 4:7 \u201cAn heir of God through Christ\u201d",
    "question": "But when the ____ of the time was come, God sent forth his Son, made of a woman, made under the law",
    "options": [
      "Fulness",
      "Goodness",
      "Beginning",
      "End"
    ],
    "answer": "Fulness",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "540f403d-43d5-492f-a42e-6d37c76f298d",
    "reference": "24- Galatians 5:1 Standing in the liberty of Christ",
    "question": "But it is good to be _____ affected always in a good thing, and not only when I am present with you.",
    "options": [
      "Patiently",
      "Beautifully",
      "Zealously",
      "Kindly"
    ],
    "answer": "Zealously",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b2dc7560-3d27-4718-b84a-7e6ee19b1783",
    "reference": "24- Galatians 5:1 Standing in the liberty of Christ",
    "question": "So then, brethren, we are not children of the ____, but of the free.",
    "options": [
      "Devil",
      "Bondwoman",
      "Enemy",
      "World"
    ],
    "answer": "Bondwoman",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5b7c6b2a-018e-4974-a097-b00d868dc4a1",
    "reference": "25- Ephesians 5:1 \u201cBe imitators of God\u201d",
    "question": "I have ____ in you through the Lord, that ye will be none otherwise minded: but he that troubleth you shall bear his judgment, whosoever ye be.",
    "options": [
      "Confidence",
      "Faith",
      "Expectation",
      "Trust"
    ],
    "answer": "Confidence",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2e5c91ab-db01-4e47-ad58-7579c79287ae",
    "reference": "25- Ephesians 5:1 \u201cBe imitators of God\u201d",
    "question": "And grieve not the ____ of God, whereby ye are sealed unto the day of redemption.",
    "options": [
      "Pastor",
      "Holy Spirit",
      "Prophet",
      "Son"
    ],
    "answer": "Holy Spirit",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f3c4bc15-46f1-484f-8c50-9e3875815876",
    "reference": "25- Ephesians 5:1 \u201cBe imitators of God\u201d",
    "question": "How must children of God walk?",
    "options": [
      "As kings and queens",
      "As humble people",
      "As children of light",
      "As Obedient children"
    ],
    "answer": "As children of light",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fe4edb7b-6972-4683-891f-584b99cf95ba",
    "reference": "26- Matthew 11:28 \u201cI will give you rest\u201d",
    "question": "Redeeming the time, because the days are ____.",
    "options": [
      "Evil",
      "Numbered",
      "Good",
      "Blessed"
    ],
    "answer": "Evil",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6171e4dd-21d6-4390-870f-b0973342d12c",
    "reference": "26- Matthew 11:28 \u201cI will give you rest\u201d",
    "question": "And blessed is he, whosoever shall not be ___ in me.",
    "options": [
      "Cursed",
      "Offended",
      "Abandoned",
      "Converted"
    ],
    "answer": "Offended",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7dc9ae1a-cecb-4155-8352-807baa74854f",
    "reference": "27- Psalm 46:10 \u201cBe still, and know that I am God\u201d",
    "question": "Think not that I am come to send peace on earth: I came not to send peace, but a ____.",
    "options": [
      "Prophet",
      "God",
      "Son",
      "Sword"
    ],
    "answer": "Sword",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "03499104-b904-4239-8c4a-d0b1f80ed7b3",
    "reference": "27- Psalm 46:10 \u201cBe still, and know that I am God\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord of hosts is with us; the God of Jacob is our ___.",
    "options": [
      "Strength",
      "Youth",
      "Refuge",
      "Provision"
    ],
    "answer": "Refuge",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f448c5ae-825f-4b13-9aa9-0a70bafb2855",
    "reference": "28- Psalm 100: 5 \u201cHis truth endures to all generations\u201d",
    "question": "God is our refuge and ____, a very present help in trouble.",
    "options": [
      "Strength",
      "Provider",
      "Protector",
      "Redeemer"
    ],
    "answer": "Strength",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f3d2500c-f583-4ac5-a72f-375a11f32bb3",
    "reference": "28- Psalm 100: 5 \u201cHis truth endures to all generations\u201d",
    "question": "Exalt the Lord our God, and ____ at his holy hill; for the Lord our God is holy.",
    "options": [
      "Praise",
      "Seek",
      "Worship",
      "Come"
    ],
    "answer": "Worship",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d30ab234-cf7b-46c3-861c-00d271716aac",
    "reference": "28- Psalm 100: 5 \u201cHis truth endures to all generations\u201d",
    "question": "How must we enter God gates?",
    "options": [
      "With praise",
      "With thanksgiving",
      "a & b",
      "With offerings"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2af3d08a-f1e4-429a-b218-61d802370bfe",
    "reference": "28- Psalm 100: 5 \u201cHis truth endures to all generations\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord is my strength and my shield; my heart ___ in him, and I am helped:",
    "options": [
      "Looked",
      "Trusted",
      "Worshiped",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Trusted",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "17576315-b544-4395-9564-73ba89b232b6",
    "reference": "28- Psalm 100: 5 \u201cHis truth endures to all generations\u201d",
    "question": "The voice of the Lord ____ the flames of fire.",
    "options": [
      "Stopped",
      "Calmed",
      "Blew",
      "Divideth"
    ],
    "answer": "Divideth",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "68e40161-b26e-4be2-96b1-284d8a8b28d3",
    "reference": "28- Psalm 100: 5 \u201cHis truth endures to all generations\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord will give strength unto his people; the Lord will bless his people with ___.",
    "options": [
      "Wisdom",
      "Peace",
      "Money",
      "Power"
    ],
    "answer": "Peace",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b32f5c29-992e-4c4d-8aa1-e8a3c8248fa4",
    "reference": "1- Psalm 107:8 \u201cGive thanks to the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "Nevertheless he ____ their affliction, when he heard their cry:",
    "options": [
      "Ignored",
      "Saw",
      "Laughed at",
      "Regarded"
    ],
    "answer": "Regarded",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d1742e7b-1931-4bf5-b0ec-97b0303db41a",
    "reference": "1- Psalm 107:8 \u201cGive thanks to the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "And he ___ them forth by the right way, that they might go to a city of habitation.",
    "options": [
      "Brought",
      "Led",
      "Acknowledge",
      "Forgave"
    ],
    "answer": "Led",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "16384450-83f4-480f-a1b0-0a62ad4b5628",
    "reference": "2- Isaiah 55:11 \u201c[My word] shall not return to me void\u201d",
    "question": "Oh that men would ___ the Lord for his goodness, and for his wonderful works to the children of men!",
    "options": [
      "Worship",
      "Thank",
      "Sing to",
      "Praise"
    ],
    "answer": "Praise",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6f5accd8-8eec-4504-bf3c-17e199b4008a",
    "reference": "2- Isaiah 55:11 \u201c[My word] shall not return to me void\u201d",
    "question": "Behold, I have given him for a ____ to the people, a leader and a commander to the people.",
    "options": [
      "Soldier",
      "Representative",
      "Witness",
      "Pastor"
    ],
    "answer": "Witness",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d05acb6c-6534-4ee9-8307-1f12715b2fdd",
    "reference": "2- Isaiah 55:11 \u201c[My word] shall not return to me void\u201d",
    "question": "No weapon that is formed against thee shall ___; and every tongue that shall rise against thee in judgment thou shalt condemn.",
    "options": [
      "Succeed",
      "Stand",
      "Work",
      "Prosper"
    ],
    "answer": "Prosper",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "29c397cf-6929-40ae-a8c9-8df651b7fbe5",
    "reference": "3- Ezekiel 36:27 \u201cI will put My Spirit within you\u201d",
    "question": "Seek ye the Lord while he may be ____, call ye upon him while he is near.",
    "options": [
      "Known",
      "Famous",
      "Found",
      "Stronger"
    ],
    "answer": "Found",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4263fa08-9614-4e4f-85b7-2ee458fbc3d7",
    "reference": "3- Ezekiel 36:27 \u201cI will put My Spirit within you\u201d",
    "question": "But I had ___ for mine holy name, which the house of Israel had profaned among the heathen, whither they went.",
    "options": [
      "Favors",
      "Forgiveness",
      "Punishment",
      "Pity"
    ],
    "answer": "Pity",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "bcf1127d-2916-46d1-add6-0faf5c3e97ee",
    "reference": "4- Psalm 119:11 \u201cYour word I have hidden in my heart\u201d",
    "question": "Not for your ____ do I this, saith the Lord God, be it known unto you: be ashamed and confounded for your own ways, O house of Israel.",
    "options": [
      "Name",
      "Father",
      "Compassion",
      "Sakes"
    ],
    "answer": "Sakes",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8d490e4a-8a3e-4fd6-88c4-352cc2a60fc5",
    "reference": "4- Psalm 119:11 \u201cYour word I have hidden in my heart\u201d",
    "question": "____ are they that keep his testimonies, and that seek him with the whole heart.",
    "options": [
      "Gracious",
      "Blessed",
      "Faithful",
      "Honored"
    ],
    "answer": "Blessed",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e0843e25-d5af-45c0-a18c-605a89f3e7eb",
    "reference": "4- Psalm 119:11 \u201cYour word I have hidden in my heart\u201d",
    "question": "Thy testimonies also are my ____ and my counselors.",
    "options": [
      "Prayer",
      "Hope",
      "Delight",
      "Privilege"
    ],
    "answer": "Delight",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3a176b52-0b89-4700-864c-ac3db7762825",
    "reference": "5- Psalm 119: 33-40 \u201cTeach me, O LORD, the way of your statutes\u201d",
    "question": "O give ___ unto the Lord; for he is good: for his mercy endureth for ever",
    "options": [
      "Thoughts",
      "Praise",
      "Thanks",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Thanks",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "15b2ddc1-367d-45d5-83be-451371301b35",
    "reference": "5- Psalm 119: 33-40 \u201cTeach me, O LORD, the way of your statutes\u201d",
    "question": "Remove from me the way of ____: and grant me thy law graciously.",
    "options": [
      "Shame",
      "Lying",
      "Regret",
      "Sorrow"
    ],
    "answer": "Lying",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cb810d66-ad29-45f6-979e-a4c8c2ca0d78",
    "reference": "5- Psalm 119: 33-40 \u201cTeach me, O LORD, the way of your statutes\u201d",
    "question": "____my heart unto thy testimonies, and not to covetousness.",
    "options": [
      "Open",
      "Brighten",
      "Incline",
      "Support"
    ],
    "answer": "Incline",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fadde30f-1740-4c0e-8a4c-ca6df946a5e9",
    "reference": "6- Micah 7:19 \u201c[God] will cast all our sins into the depths of the sea\u201d",
    "question": "I will speak of thy _____ also before kings, and will not be ashamed.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Testimonies",
      "Grace",
      "Power"
    ],
    "answer": "Testimonies",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a9d52102-7bdf-4f81-a603-e9c6923bd7df",
    "reference": "6- Micah 7:19 \u201c[God] will cast all our sins into the depths of the sea\u201d",
    "question": "Therefore I will look unto the Lord; I will wait for the God of my salvation: my God will ___ me.",
    "options": [
      "Bless",
      "Support",
      "Uphold",
      "Hear"
    ],
    "answer": "Hear",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "681c4990-8e58-466a-aa88-5202115ac490",
    "reference": "7- Proverbs 30:6 \u201cDo not add to [God\u2019s] words\u201d",
    "question": "According to the days of thy coming out of the land of Egypt will I shew unto him ____ things.",
    "options": [
      "Bright",
      "Marvelous",
      "Wicked",
      "Original"
    ],
    "answer": "Marvelous",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b2e56d18-3e24-4df4-838a-d2cd6747ca09",
    "reference": "7- Proverbs 30:6 \u201cDo not add to [God\u2019s] words\u201d",
    "question": "Two things have I ____ of thee; deny me them not before I die:",
    "options": [
      "Asked",
      "Required",
      "Demanded",
      "Hoped"
    ],
    "answer": "Required",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c855ef03-4927-4e16-a6f8-21ad44d0c43e",
    "reference": "7- Proverbs 30:6 \u201cDo not add to [God\u2019s] words\u201d",
    "question": "Every word of God is ___: he is a shield unto them that put their trust in him",
    "options": [
      "Authentic",
      "Merciful",
      "Pure",
      "Truthful"
    ],
    "answer": "Pure",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "00adaee1-77f9-4027-a39e-553a4fa6eee4",
    "reference": "8- Proverbs 18:21 \u201cDeath and life are in the power of the tongue\u201d",
    "question": "A man's ___ shall bring him low:  but honor shall uphold the humble in spirit.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Pride",
      "Shame",
      "Strength"
    ],
    "answer": "Pride",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f4838028-1bbf-4785-9ffd-a090978a98c5",
    "reference": "8- Proverbs 18:21 \u201cDeath and life are in the power of the tongue\u201d",
    "question": "___ is the poor that walketh in his integrity, than he that is perverse in his lips, and is a fool.",
    "options": [
      "Lucky",
      "Honor",
      "Kind",
      "Better"
    ],
    "answer": "Better",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "93e64102-b575-4fba-b499-311d190abeed",
    "reference": "9- James 1: 5 \u201cIf any of you lacks wisdom, let him ask of God\u201d",
    "question": "A brother offended is ____ to be won than a strong city: and their contentions are like the bars of a castle.",
    "options": [
      "Harder",
      "Better",
      "Preferable",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Harder",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "835be9d0-f64c-4643-8056-4cc94b72a336",
    "reference": "9- James 1: 5 \u201cIf any of you lacks wisdom, let him ask of God\u201d",
    "question": "Knowing this, that the trying of your faith worketh ___.",
    "options": [
      "Strength",
      "Patience",
      "Grace",
      "Peace"
    ],
    "answer": "Patience",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "25a83962-0179-490e-90fd-fdc023adc30c",
    "reference": "9- James 1: 5 \u201cIf any of you lacks wisdom, let him ask of God\u201d",
    "question": "Can God be tempted by evil?",
    "options": [
      "Not sure",
      "Sometimes",
      "No",
      "Yes"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "880053af-053b-4f2e-a234-fe368c23a9fc",
    "reference": "10- Jeremiah 31:31 God Will Make a Covenant with You",
    "question": "What kind of gift is from above?",
    "options": [
      "Good",
      "Perfect",
      "Mysterious",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4f730649-d989-42e9-a605-9d6fbdd35332",
    "reference": "10- Jeremiah 31:31 God Will Make a Covenant with You",
    "question": "For I have satiated the weary soul, and I have ____ every sorrowful soul.",
    "options": [
      "Remembered",
      "Sanctified",
      "Replenished",
      "Loved"
    ],
    "answer": "Replenished",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "abedd3c8-81a5-4bca-8b77-6a3567247b66",
    "reference": "11- A Study on the Names of God: Exodus 6:2-3 \u201cI am the LORD\u201d (JEHOVAH)",
    "question": "And there is ___ in thine end, saith the Lord, that thy children shall come again to their own border.",
    "options": [
      "Hope",
      "Favor",
      "Life",
      "Light"
    ],
    "answer": "Hope",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "469536fc-14cf-4bf7-bba9-eb9afa0bd9c0",
    "reference": "11- A Study on the Names of God: Exodus 6:2-3 \u201cI am the LORD\u201d (JEHOVAH)",
    "question": "How was God known to Abraham, Isaac and Jacob as?",
    "options": [
      "King",
      "Christ",
      "God Almighty",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "God Almighty",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f29783c0-4432-475e-bef3-cbafa15d93c2",
    "reference": "11- A Study on the Names of God: Exodus 6:2-3 \u201cI am the LORD\u201d (JEHOVAH)",
    "question": "Which land did God promise Abraham and his descendants?",
    "options": [
      "Land of Israel",
      "Land of Canaan",
      "Land of Egypt",
      "Land of Jerusalem"
    ],
    "answer": "Land of Canaan",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "08e3a24c-0796-4826-9936-e59acbba13d8",
    "reference": "12- Jeremiah 23:6 \u201cThe LORD Our Righteousness\u201d (JEHOVAH TSIDKENU)",
    "question": "And Moses returned unto the Lord, and said, Lord, wherefore hast thou so ___ entreated this people? Why is that thou hast sent me?",
    "options": [
      "Pleasure",
      "Disastrous",
      "Vulgar",
      "Evil"
    ],
    "answer": "Evil",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5d3adab7-066b-402f-8a2c-4cfad8b9055e",
    "reference": "12- Jeremiah 23:6 \u201cThe LORD Our Righteousness\u201d (JEHOVAH TSIDKENU)",
    "question": "Mine heart within me is ___ because of the prophets; all my bones shake; I am like a drunken man, and like a man whom wine hath overcome, because of the Lord, and because of the words of his holiness.",
    "options": [
      "Alive",
      "Joyful",
      "Broken",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Broken",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "625db19c-847b-449a-ad0c-b093a559a47c",
    "reference": "12- Jeremiah 23:6 \u201cThe LORD Our Righteousness\u201d (JEHOVAH TSIDKENU)",
    "question": "Behold, the days come, saith the Lord, that I will raise unto ____ a righteous branch, and a King shall reign and prosper, and shall execute judgment and justice in the earth.",
    "options": [
      "Abraham",
      "David",
      "Jacob",
      "Moses"
    ],
    "answer": "David",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f8a07cd6-dce9-4121-99c1-a7df0e223b90",
    "reference": "13- Exodus 15:26 \u201cI am the LORD who heals you\u201d (JEHOVAH RAPHA)",
    "question": "Woe be unto the ____ that destroy and scatter the sheep of my pasture! Saith the Lord.",
    "options": [
      "Pastors",
      "Priests",
      "Preachers",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Pastors",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0b9c6a8b-baf2-4e60-8353-3cb77535ca7b",
    "reference": "13- Exodus 15:26 \u201cI am the LORD who heals you\u201d (JEHOVAH RAPHA)",
    "question": "How many wells of water were there in Elim?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "15",
      "3",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "12",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4012c360-7cac-42d3-966a-bd7ba8b53a53",
    "reference": "13- Exodus 15:26 \u201cI am the LORD who heals you\u201d (JEHOVAH RAPHA)",
    "question": "Who was Miriam?",
    "options": [
      "A prophetess",
      "Aaron's sister",
      "Aaron's wife",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "be124160-caee-47a2-8282-494db6b3a150",
    "reference": "14- Genesis 22: 12-14 The LORD Who Provides (JEHOVAH JIREH)",
    "question": "The Lord is my strength and song, and he is become my ___: he is my God, and I will prepare him an habitation; my father's God, and I will exalt him.",
    "options": [
      "Refuge",
      "Salvation",
      "Redeemer",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "Salvation",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "52245385-1ecc-4253-ae22-b9e08b7ccc16",
    "reference": "14- Genesis 22: 12-14 The LORD Who Provides (JEHOVAH JIREH)",
    "question": "What did God ask Abraham as offering?",
    "options": [
      "Isaac",
      "A Lamb",
      "Fruits",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Isaac",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6e29ba43-ba1d-4bd8-a541-51f043775e1c",
    "reference": "14- Genesis 22: 12-14 The LORD Who Provides (JEHOVAH JIREH)",
    "question": "What was Abraham answer to Isaac question 'Where is the lamb?'?",
    "options": [
      "You are the lamb",
      "Stay quiet",
      "I don't know",
      "The lord will provide himself a lamb"
    ],
    "answer": "The lord will provide himself a lamb",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5b6e3845-298c-4982-ab80-897c3d48f6dd",
    "reference": "15- Psalm 91:9 \u201cThe LORD who is my refuge\u201d  (JEHOVAH MACHSI)",
    "question": "Where did God ask Abraham to provide the burn offering?",
    "options": [
      "Land of Canaan",
      "Land of Egypt",
      "Land of Moriah",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Land of Moriah",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6e0ca28c-2a53-42b4-9492-570d61e0107b",
    "reference": "15- Psalm 91:9 \u201cThe LORD who is my refuge\u201d  (JEHOVAH MACHSI)",
    "question": "Let thy work appear unto thy servants, and thy ___ unto their children.",
    "options": [
      "Glory",
      "Favor",
      "Name",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Glory",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "986720c0-f4e8-4a6f-bf85-7208a9b3884e",
    "reference": "16- Judges 6:24 \u201cThe LORD is Peace\u201d (JEHOVAH SHALOM)",
    "question": "For he shall give his angels charge over thee, to keep thee in ___ thy ways.",
    "options": [
      "Any of",
      "All",
      "Some of",
      "Glorious"
    ],
    "answer": "All",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "70930f8b-06b2-4f92-9a77-fd4ab340b7a4",
    "reference": "16- Judges 6:24 \u201cThe LORD is Peace\u201d (JEHOVAH SHALOM)",
    "question": "Who built the altar unto the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "David",
      "Gideon",
      "Abraham",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Gideon",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "721a0ece-b628-4302-8fe3-9357ba7a5876",
    "reference": "16- Judges 6:24 \u201cThe LORD is Peace\u201d (JEHOVAH SHALOM)",
    "question": "And the angel of the Lord appeared unto him, and said unto him, the Lord is with thee, thou mighty man of ___.",
    "options": [
      "Grace",
      "Faith",
      "Valor",
      "Honor"
    ],
    "answer": "Valor",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1caaf2b0-5521-4abe-8761-f94a5bb7dd28",
    "reference": "17- Psalm 23:1 \u201cThe LORD is my shepherd\u201d (JEHOVAH ROHI)",
    "question": "And the Lord said unto him, Peace be unto thee; fear not: thou shalt not ___.",
    "options": [
      "Die",
      "Be punished",
      "Be mocked",
      "Be forgotten"
    ],
    "answer": "Die",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2604eae5-8f2f-4ec2-9571-9da8656959e0",
    "reference": "17- Psalm 23:1 \u201cThe LORD is my shepherd\u201d (JEHOVAH ROHI)",
    "question": "The meek shall eat and be ___: they shall praise the Lord that seek him: and none can keep alive his own soul.",
    "options": [
      "Humble",
      "Satisfied",
      "Gracious",
      "Grateful"
    ],
    "answer": "Satisfied",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7a518eb8-eb99-4598-b954-8ca1d60af21c",
    "reference": "18- Deuteronomy 33:29 \u201cThe LORD the shield\u201d  (JEHOVAH MAGEN)",
    "question": "Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me ___ the days of my life: and I will dwell in the house of the Lord for ever.",
    "options": [
      "Some of",
      "Most of",
      "All",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "11761266-f86f-4277-8ada-2ff20628ac5e",
    "reference": "18- Deuteronomy 33:29 \u201cThe LORD the shield\u201d  (JEHOVAH MAGEN)",
    "question": "What blessing did Moses pronounce on Asher?",
    "options": [
      "Children",
      "Wealth",
      "Leadership",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Children",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cd49e92d-531d-4be9-b6a3-929daafb25bb",
    "reference": "18- Deuteronomy 33:29 \u201cThe LORD the shield\u201d  (JEHOVAH MAGEN)",
    "question": "What blessing did Moses pronounce on Naphtali?",
    "options": [
      "Children",
      "Love",
      "Favor",
      "Priesthood"
    ],
    "answer": "Favor",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7cc6ed45-280b-42e4-be55-f3acd636cc56",
    "reference": "19- Judges 11:27 \u201cThe LORD the Judge\u201d (JEHOVAH HASHOPET)",
    "question": "Moses commanded us a ___, even the inheritance of the congregation of Jacob.",
    "options": [
      "Prayer",
      "Law",
      "Way",
      "Direction"
    ],
    "answer": "Law",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "da339b17-c535-44bf-9921-ddd8414cf380",
    "reference": "19- Judges 11:27 \u201cThe LORD the Judge\u201d (JEHOVAH HASHOPET)",
    "question": "Who was the king of the Amorites?",
    "options": [
      "Sihon",
      "Josuah",
      "Jephthah",
      "Moab"
    ],
    "answer": "Sihon",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f5ccccda-cc82-4237-987a-e62c2d108d2b",
    "reference": "19- Judges 11:27 \u201cThe LORD the Judge\u201d (JEHOVAH HASHOPET)",
    "question": "So now the Lord God of Israel hath ____ the Amorites from before his people Israel, and shouldest thou possess it?",
    "options": [
      "Vacated",
      "Occupied",
      "Dispossessed",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Dispossessed",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2220eb07-0e78-44a7-81ef-31c636f653f6",
    "reference": "20- Isaiah 49:26 \u201cThe LORD \u2026 your Redeemer\u201d (JEHOVAH GOEL)",
    "question": "So Jephthah passed over unto the children of Ammon to fight against them; and the Lord ___ them into his hands.",
    "options": [
      "Remember",
      "Delivereth",
      "Forgave",
      "Bless"
    ],
    "answer": "Delivereth",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2be134aa-2094-4007-b286-ee37a448220b",
    "reference": "20- Isaiah 49:26 \u201cThe LORD \u2026 your Redeemer\u201d (JEHOVAH GOEL)",
    "question": "Can a woman ___ her sucking child, that she should not have compassion on the son of her womb? Yea, they may forget, yet will I not forget thee.",
    "options": [
      "Forget",
      "Punish",
      "Discipline",
      "Mislead"
    ],
    "answer": "Forget",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9a1acf29-284a-47d6-b187-6089a602f120",
    "reference": "21- Exodus 31:13 \u201cI am the LORD who sanctifies you\u201d (JEHOVAH M\u2019GADDISCHEM)",
    "question": "Thus saith the Lord God, behold, I will lift up mine hand to the ___, and set up my standard to the people: and they shall bring thy sons in their arms, and thy daughters shall be carried upon their shoulders.",
    "options": [
      "Afflicted",
      "Gentiles",
      "Poor",
      "Needy"
    ],
    "answer": "Gentiles",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "40968d2f-b246-4ff2-8e16-96fb3eca5aa7",
    "reference": "21- Exodus 31:13 \u201cI am the LORD who sanctifies you\u201d (JEHOVAH M\u2019GADDISCHEM)",
    "question": "And the ___ oil, and sweet incense for the holy place: according to all that I have commanded thee shall they do.",
    "options": [
      "Anointed",
      "Palm",
      "Crude",
      "Blazing"
    ],
    "answer": "Anointed",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ce08a1c9-230d-4e4e-bc87-ed55294c2a05",
    "reference": "21- Exodus 31:13 \u201cI am the LORD who sanctifies you\u201d (JEHOVAH M\u2019GADDISCHEM)",
    "question": "How many days are meant for work?",
    "options": [
      "Five",
      "Six",
      "Three",
      "Seven"
    ],
    "answer": "Six",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "337a1c91-7607-4a1e-9cc2-873605a7aa9a",
    "reference": "22- 1 Samuel 1:3 \u201cThe LORD of Hosts\u201d (JEHOVAH SABAOTH)",
    "question": "Where was the commandments pass onto Moses?",
    "options": [
      "Mount Olive",
      "Red Sea",
      "Mount Sinai",
      "In his dream"
    ],
    "answer": "Mount Sinai",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "970532fb-0f04-408b-8421-a637a1c18b5a",
    "reference": "22- 1 Samuel 1:3 \u201cThe LORD of Hosts\u201d (JEHOVAH SABAOTH)",
    "question": "What is the names of Eli's sons who were also priests?",
    "options": [
      "Benjamin",
      "Hophni",
      "Phinehas",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fe2eb162-e22a-4217-bf5b-488fe574fe0a",
    "reference": "22- 1 Samuel 1:3 \u201cThe LORD of Hosts\u201d (JEHOVAH SABAOTH)",
    "question": "Who was Hannah husband?",
    "options": [
      "Israel",
      "Elkanah",
      "Eli",
      "Hophni"
    ],
    "answer": "Elkanah",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a5abf31e-72e7-41d4-87f7-f2884f357c2d",
    "reference": "23- Psalm 47:2 \u201cThe LORD Most High\u201d (JEHOVAH ELYON)",
    "question": "Where did Eli go to worship yearly?",
    "options": [
      "Mount Sinai",
      "Mount Olive",
      "Shiloh",
      "Red Sea"
    ],
    "answer": "Shiloh",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "63171523-1e28-4fe5-8415-a4ca17875559",
    "reference": "23- Psalm 47:2 \u201cThe LORD Most High\u201d (JEHOVAH ELYON)",
    "question": "The Lord of hosts is with us; the God of Jacob is our ___.",
    "options": [
      "Refuge",
      "Strength",
      "Provider",
      "Redeemer"
    ],
    "answer": "Refuge",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9ab78b04-982e-4877-90f6-2c756706ba23",
    "reference": "24- Isaiah 40:28 \u201cThe LORD, the Creator of the ends of the earth\u201d (JEHOVAH BARA)",
    "question": "For God is the ____ of all the earth: sing ye praises with understanding.",
    "options": [
      "Savior",
      "Lord",
      "King",
      "Master"
    ],
    "answer": "King",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "78041b88-3da2-46bc-8453-8043d6d722d4",
    "reference": "24- Isaiah 40:28 \u201cThe LORD, the Creator of the ends of the earth\u201d (JEHOVAH BARA)",
    "question": "What shall stand forever?",
    "options": [
      "House of worship",
      "House of orphans",
      "Word of God",
      "Jesus"
    ],
    "answer": "Word of God",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ceb475ac-335b-4397-a052-eea8ee736468",
    "reference": "24- Isaiah 40:28 \u201cThe LORD, the Creator of the ends of the earth\u201d (JEHOVAH BARA)",
    "question": "Who shall renew their strength?",
    "options": [
      "Those who serve God",
      "Those who wait upon the Lord",
      "Those who spread the gospel",
      "Those who are poor in spirit"
    ],
    "answer": "Those who wait upon the Lord",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d8b40a7d-50ea-4725-9c41-19de247c476e",
    "reference": "25- Joshua 3:13 \u201cThe LORD, the Lord of all the earth\u201d (JEHOVAH ADON KAL HA\u2019ARETS)",
    "question": "The grass withereth, the flower fadeth: because the spirit of the Lord bloweth upon it: surely the people is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Foolish",
      "Important",
      "Kind",
      "Grass"
    ],
    "answer": "Grass",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e7c1da1f-d680-4aef-a722-db0830736388",
    "reference": "25- Joshua 3:13 \u201cThe LORD, the Lord of all the earth\u201d (JEHOVAH ADON KAL HA\u2019ARETS)",
    "question": "To whom did Josuah order to carry the ark of covenant?",
    "options": [
      "The lawyers",
      "The king",
      "The priests",
      "Moses"
    ],
    "answer": "The priests",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ea92d1d6-faa9-48e5-945e-448aaea7316d",
    "reference": "25- Joshua 3:13 \u201cThe LORD, the Lord of all the earth\u201d (JEHOVAH ADON KAL HA\u2019ARETS)",
    "question": "And Josuah said unto the children of Israel, come hither, and ___ the words of the Lord your God.",
    "options": [
      "Listen",
      "Hear",
      "Know",
      "Appreciate"
    ],
    "answer": "Hear",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9efba6bc-0093-4bee-9674-2c7a57a5b382",
    "reference": "26- Psalm 98:6 \u201cThe LORD, the King\u201d (JEHOVAH HAMELECH)",
    "question": "How many men did the Lord ask Josuah to choose from the tribes of Israel?",
    "options": [
      "Seven",
      "Five",
      "Twelve",
      "Eight"
    ],
    "answer": "Twelve",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5a01424f-02b0-46d7-97d6-22f41c101a7d",
    "reference": "26- Psalm 98:6 \u201cThe LORD, the King\u201d (JEHOVAH HAMELECH)",
    "question": "Rejoice in the Lord, ye righteous; and give thanks at the remembrance of his ___.",
    "options": [
      "Name",
      "Son",
      "Holiness",
      "Grace"
    ],
    "answer": "Holiness",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a8af9beb-26d3-437c-8a4e-ad7f34b09430",
    "reference": "26- Psalm 98:6 \u201cThe LORD, the King\u201d (JEHOVAH HAMELECH)",
    "question": "Sing unto the Lord with the harp; with the harp, and the voice of a ___.",
    "options": [
      "King",
      "Psalm",
      "Princess",
      "Servant"
    ],
    "answer": "Psalm",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "654042ee-670e-4aa8-90e6-de940a6f0b2f",
    "reference": "27- Psalm 10:16 The LORD King Forever (JEHOVAH HELECH-OLAM)",
    "question": "Let the floods clap their hands: let the hills be __ together.",
    "options": [
      "Great",
      "Glorious",
      "Joyful",
      "Close"
    ],
    "answer": "Joyful",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "dea87f0e-b572-48cf-8203-af893f908bef",
    "reference": "27- Psalm 10:16 The LORD King Forever (JEHOVAH HELECH-OLAM)",
    "question": "For the wicked ___ of his heart's desire, and blesseth the covetous, whom the Lord abhoreth.",
    "options": [
      "Boasteth",
      "Enjoy",
      "Laughed",
      "Brave"
    ],
    "answer": "Boasteth",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d4a3304e-6734-48ac-bab5-1aeb8cbc83e2",
    "reference": "27- Psalm 10:16 The LORD King Forever (JEHOVAH HELECH-OLAM)",
    "question": "Arise, O Lord; O God, lift up thine hand: forget not the ___.",
    "options": [
      "Poor",
      "Humble",
      "Homeless",
      "Needy"
    ],
    "answer": "Humble",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cfb5c801-ce08-4ad1-9691-cdfe574ef553",
    "reference": "28- Psalm 24:8 \u201cThe LORD strong and mighty\u201d (JEHOVAH \u02caIZOA HAKABOTH)",
    "question": "For the righteous Lord ___ righteousness; his countenance doth behold the upright.",
    "options": [
      "Loveth",
      "Seek",
      "Worship",
      "Like"
    ],
    "answer": "Loveth",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3d912489-34bb-4959-859a-012f7d02bc72",
    "reference": "28- Psalm 24:8 \u201cThe LORD strong and mighty\u201d (JEHOVAH \u02caIZOA HAKABOTH)",
    "question": "What will not return void?",
    "options": [
      "Our gifts",
      "Our prayers",
      "God's word",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "God's word",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "70d0d62d-c62b-434d-aa05-7f4c2322b433",
    "reference": "29- Psalm 27:1 \u201cThe LORD is the strength of my life\u201d (JEHOVAH CHATSAHI)",
    "question": "What will the redeemed of the Lord do?",
    "options": [
      "Say so",
      "Shout with the voice of triumph",
      "Come with singing to Zion",
      "Keep His commandments"
    ],
    "answer": "Come with singing to Zion",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a8dd179f-3386-4155-b04f-857c5ba7982c",
    "reference": "29- Psalm 27:1 \u201cThe LORD is the strength of my life\u201d (JEHOVAH CHATSAHI)",
    "question": "Gather not my soul with ___, nor my life with bloody men:",
    "options": [
      "Jokers",
      "Sinners",
      "Unkind",
      "Hypocrites"
    ],
    "answer": "Sinners",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "914c77bb-b1f3-4dd8-88b8-a4ac8369ad04",
    "reference": "30- Psalm 27:1 \u201cThe LORD is my light\u201d (JEHOVAH \u02caORI)",
    "question": "When my father and mother ___ me, the Lord will take me up.",
    "options": [
      "Forsake",
      "Ignore",
      "Abandon",
      "Punish"
    ],
    "answer": "Forsake",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "bf52dc74-eeb2-44f2-91d0-5b8c73774870",
    "reference": "30- Psalm 27:1 \u201cThe LORD is my light\u201d (JEHOVAH \u02caORI)",
    "question": "Wait on the Lord: be of good courage, and he shall ____ thine heart: wait, I say, on the Lord.",
    "options": [
      "Remember",
      "Strengthen",
      "Bless",
      "Protect"
    ],
    "answer": "Strengthen",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "48f03645-9fdc-4a5c-b34a-d58c9f7dbd6d",
    "reference": "31- Psalm 3:3 The LORD my Glory (JEHOVAH KABODHI)",
    "question": "Hear the voice of my ___, when I cry unto thee, when I lift up my hands toward thy holy oracle.",
    "options": [
      "Supplications",
      "Father",
      "Mother",
      "Brother"
    ],
    "answer": "Supplications",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fb12bc86-f626-4803-9f65-16552475154b",
    "reference": "31- Psalm 3:3 The LORD my Glory (JEHOVAH KABODHI)",
    "question": "Let all the earth fear the Lord: let all the inhabitants of the world ___ in awe of him.",
    "options": [
      "Fear",
      "Applaud",
      "Stand",
      "Support"
    ],
    "answer": "Stand",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3587b760-ea6e-4737-bb68-d4046393d4f5",
    "reference": "31- Psalm 3:3 The LORD my Glory (JEHOVAH KABODHI)",
    "question": "Many sorrows shall be to the wicked: but he that ___ in the Lord, mercy shall compass him about.",
    "options": [
      "Worship",
      "Trusteth",
      "Seek",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Trusteth",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ca61acde-76cf-42b7-bd61-e3f689f3316b",
    "reference": "31- Psalm 3:3 The LORD my Glory (JEHOVAH KABODHI)",
    "question": "What does God love?",
    "options": [
      "His creation",
      "Righteousness",
      "Judgment",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q1",
    "month": ""
  }
]